"Once upon a time there was a lovely princess
"But she had an enchantment upon her of a fearful sort...
"which could only be broken by love's first kiss.
"She was locked away in a castle...
"guarded by a terrible fire-breathing dragon.
"Many brave knights had attempted to free her from this deadful prison.
"but none prevailed.
"She waited in the dragon's keep...
"in the highest room of the tallest tower...
for her true love and true love's first kiss. "
Like that's ever gonna happen
- What a load of -
Somebody once told me
the world is gonna roll me
I ain't the sharpest tool
in the shed
She was lookin' kind of dumb
with her finger and her thumb
In the shape of an "L"
on the forehead
The years start comin'
and they don't stop commin'
Fed to the rules
and I hit the ground runnin'
Didn't make sense
not live for fun
Your brain gets smart
but your head gets dumb
So much to do
So much to see
So what's wrong with
takin' the backstreets
You'll never know
if you don't go
You'll never shine
if you don't glow
Hey, now
You're an all-star
Get your game on, go play
Hey, now, you're a rock star
Get the show on, get paid
And all that glitter is gold
Only shootin' stars
break the mould
It's a cool place and they say it gets colder
You're bundled up now but wait till you get older
But the meteor men beg to differ
Judging by the hole
in the satellite picture
The ice we skate
is gettin' pretty thin
The water's getting warm
so you might as well swim
My world's on fire
How 'bout yours
That's the way I like it
and I'll never get bored
- Hey, now, you're an all-star
Get your game on go play
Hey, now you're a rock star
Get the show on, get paid
And all that glitter is gold
Only shootin' stars break the mould
- Go!
- Go. Go. Go.
Hey, now You're an all-star
Get your game on, go play
Hey, now, you're a rock star
Get the show on, get paid
And all that glitter is gold
Only shootin' stars break the mould
- Think it's in there?
- All right. Let's get it!
Whoa, Hold on. Do you know
what thing can do to you?
Yeah, it'll grind
your bones for its bread.
Yes, well, actually,
that would be a giant.
Now, ogres-
They're much worse.
They'll make a suit
from your freshly peeled skin.
- No!
- They'll shave your liver.
Squeeze the
jelly from your eyes!
- Actualy, it's quite good on toast.
- Back! Back, beast!
Back! I warn ya!
-Right.
This is the part
where you run away.
And stay out!
"Wanted. Fairy tale creatures. "
All right. This one's full
- Take it away!
- Move it along. Come on! Get up!
- Next!
Give me that! Your flying days are over.
That's 20 pieces of silver
for the witch. Next!
- Get up! Come on!
- Twenty pieces.
- Sit down there!
- Keep quiet!
This cage is too small.
Please don't turn me in.
I'll never be stubborn again.
I can change.
Please! Give ma another chance!
-Oh, shut up.
-Oh! - Next!
-What have you got?
- This little wooden puppet.
I'm not a puppet. I'm a real boy.
Five shillings forthe possessed toy.
- Take it away.
- Father, please! Don't let them do this!
- Help me!
- Next. What have you got?
- Well, I've got a talking donkey.
Right. Well, that's good for
ten shillings, if you can prouve it.
Oh, go ahead, little fella.
Well?
Oh, oh, he's just-
He's just a little nervous.
He's really quite a chatterbox. Talk, you boneheaded dolt-
- That's it. I've heard enough. Guards!
-No, no, he talks!
He does. I can talk. I love to talk.
I'm the talkingest
damn thing you ever saw.
- Get her out of my sight.
-No, no!
I swear! Oh! He can talk!
Hey! I can fly!
- He can fly!
- He can talk!
Ha, ha! That's right, fool!
Now I'm a flying, talking donkey.
Your right have seen a house fly
maybe even a super fly,
but I bet you ain't never seen a donkey fly.
Ha, ha!
Uh-oh.
Seize him!
After him!
He's getting away!
Get him! This way! Turn!
You there. Ogre!
Aye?
By the order of Lord Farquaad, I am
authorized to place you under arrest...
and transport you to
a designated... resettlement facility.
Oh, really?
You and what army?
Can I say something to you?
Listen, you was really, really somethin'
back there. Incredible!
Are you talkin' to-
me? Whoa!
Yes, I was talkin' to you. Can I tell you
that you was great back there? Those guards!
They thought they was all of that.
Then you showed up, and bam!
They was trippin' over themselves
like babes in the woods.
That really made me
feel good to see that.
- Oh, that's great. Really.
- Man, it's good to be free.
Now, why don't you go celebrate your
freedom with your own friends? Hmm?
But, uh, I don't have any friends.
And I'm not goin' out there by myself.
Hey, wait a minute! I got
a great idea! I'll stick with you.
You're a mean, green, fightin' machine.
Together we'll scare
the spit out of anybody that crosses us.
Oh, wow! That was really scary.
If you don't mind me sayin' if that don(t work,
your breath certainly will get the job done,
'cause you definitely need some Tic Tacs
or something, 'cause your breath stinks!
You almost burned the hair outta my nose,
just like the time-
Then I ate some rotten berries. I had
strong gases eking out of my butt that day.
Why are you following me?
I'll tell you why.
'Cause I'm all alone
There's no one here beside me
My problems have all gone
There's no one to deride me
But you gotta have friend-
Stop singing!
It's no wonder
you don't have any friends.
Wow. Only a true friend
would be that truly honest.
Listen, little donkey.
Take a look at me. What am I?
Uh-
-Really tall?
- No! I'm an ogre.
You know.
"Grab your torch and pitchforks. "
Doesn't that bother you?
Nope.
- Really?
- Really,really.
- Oh.
- Man, I like you. What's your name?
Uh, Shrek.
Shrek? Well, you know
what I like about you, Shrek?
You got a kind of I-don't-care-what-nobody-
thinks-of-me thing.
I like that.
I respect that, Shrek. You alright.
Whoo! Look at that. Who'd want
to live in a place like that?
That would be my home.
Oh! And it is lovely!
Just beautiful.
You are quite a decorator. It's amazing
what you've done with such a modest budget.
I like that boulder.
That is a nice boulder.
I guess you don't
entertain much, do you?
I like my privacy.
You know, I do too.
That's another thing we have in comon.
Like, I hate it when
you got somebody in your face.
You're trying to give them a hint, and they
won't leave. There's that awkward silence.
- Can I stay with you?
- Uh, what?
Can I stay with you, please?
- Of course!
- Really?
- No.
- Please! I don't wanna go back there!
You don't know what it's like to be
considered a freak. Well, maybe you do.
But that's why we gotta stick together. You gotta let me stay!
- Please! Please!
- Okay! Okay!
- But one night only.
- Ah! Thank you!
- What are you- No! No!
- This is gonna be fun!
We can stay up late, swappin' manly stories,
and in the mornin' I'm makin' waffles.
- Oh!
- Where do, uh, I sleep?
Outside!
Oh,well,
I guess that's cool.
I mean, I don't know you,
and you don't know me,
so I guess outside is best, you know.
Here I go.
Good night.
I mean, I do like the outdoors.
I'm a donkey. I was born outside.
I'll just be sitting by myself
outside, I guess, you know.
By myself, outside.
I'm all alone.
There's no one here beside me
I thought I told you to stay outside.
- I am outside.
Well, gents, it's a far cry from
the farm, but what choice do we have?
It's not home,
but it'll do just fine.
What a lovely bed.
- Got ya.
- I found some cheese.
- Ow!
- Blah! Awful stuff.
-Is that you, Gorder?
- How did you know?
Enough!
What are you doing in my house?
Hey!
- Oh!, no, no, no.
- Dead broad off the table.
- Where are we supposed to put her? The bed's taken.
Huh?
What?
I live in a swamp. I put up signs.
I'm a terrifying ogre!
What do I have to do
to get a little privacy?
-Aah!
- Oh, no.
Oh, no.
- No! No!
- What?
- Quit it.
- Don't push.
What are you doing
in my swamp?
Swamp! Swamp! Swamp!
- Oh, dear!
Whoa!
All right, get out of here.
All of you, move it!
Come on! Let's go!
Hapaya! Hapaya! Hey!
- Quickly. Come on!
- No, no!
No, no.
Not there. Not there.
- Oh!
Hey, don't look at me. I didn't invite them.
Oh, gosh, no one invited us.
- What?
- We were forced to come here.
- By who?
- Lord Farquaad.
He huffed und he puffed und he...
signed an eviction notice.
All right.
Who knows where
this Farquaad guy is?
- Oh, I do. I know where he is.
Does anyone else
know where to find him?
- Anyone at all?
- Me! Me!
- Anyone?
- Oh! Oh, pick me!
Oh, I know! I know! Me, me!
Okay, fine.
Attention,
all fairy tale things.
Do not get comfortable.
Your welcome is officially worn out.
In fact, I'm gonna see
this guy Farquaad right now...
and get you all off my land
and back where you came from!
Oh! You!
You're comin' with me.
All right, that's
what I like to hear, man
Shrek and donkey, two stalwart friends,
off on a whirlwind big-city adventure.
I love it!
- On the road again
I can't wait to get
on the road again
What did I say
about singing?
- Can I whistle?
- No.
- Can I hum it?
- All right, hum it.
That's enough.
He's ready to talk.
Run, run, run,
as fast as you can.
You can't catch me.
I'm the gingerbread man!
- You're a monster.
- I'm not the monster here. You are.
You and the rest of that fairy tale
trash, poisoning my perfect world.
Now, tell me!
Where are the others?
- Eat me!
I've tried to be fair
to you creatures.
Now my patience has reached its end!
Tell me or I'll-
No, no, not the buttons.
Not my gumdrop buttons.
All right then.
Who's hiding them?
Okay, I'll tell you.
Do you know the muffin man?
- The muffin man?
- The muffin man.
Yes, I know the muffin man,
who lives on Drury Lane?
Well, she's married
to the muffin man.
- The muffin man?
- The muffin man!
- She's married to the muffin man.
My lord! We found it.
Then what are you waiting for?
Bring it in.
- Oh!
- Magic mirror-
- Don't tell him anything!
No!
- Evening.
Mirror, mirror, on the wall.
Is this not the most
perfect kingdom of them all?
Well, technically
you're not a king.
Uh, Thelonius.
- You were saying?
- What I mean is, you're not a king yet.
But you can become one. All
you have to do is marry a princess.
- Go on.
So, just sit back
and relax, my lord,
because it's time for you to
meet today's eligible bachelorettes.
And here they are!
Bachelorette number one is a mentally
abused shut-in from a kingdom far, far away.
She likes sushi
and hot tubbing anytime.
Her hobbies include cooking
and cleaning for her two evil sisters.
Please welcome Cinderella.
Bachelorette number two\is a cape-wearing girl
from the land of fancy.
Although she lives with
seven other men, she's not easy.
Just kiss her dead, frozen lips
and find out what a live wire she is.
Come on.
Give it up for Snow White!
And last,
but certainly not least,
bachelorette number three
is a fiery redhead...
from a dragon-guarded castle
surrounded by hot boiling lava!
But don't let that cool you off.
She's a loaded pistol who likes pina
coladas and getting caught in the rain.
Yours for the rescuing, Princess Fiona!
So will it be
bachelorette number one,
bachelorette number two or bachelorette number three?
- Two! Two!
- Three! Three!
- Three!
Three? One?
Three?
Three!
Pick number three, my lord!
Okay, okay, uh, number three!
Lord Farquaad,
you've chosen Princess Fiona.
If you love pina coladas
- And getting caught in the rain
- Princess Fiona.
- If you're not into yoga
All I have to do is
just find someone who can go-
But I probably should mention
the little thing that happens at night.
- I'll do it.
- Yes, but after sunset-
Silence! I will make
this Princess Fiona my queen,
and DuLoc will finally
have the perfect king!
Captain, assemble
your finet men.
We're going to have
a tournament.
But that's it. That'st it
right there. That's DuLoc.
I told ya I'd find it.
So, that must be
Lord Farquaad's castle.
Uh-huh. That's the place.
Do you think maybe
he's compensating for something?
Hey, wait.
Wait up, Shrek.
Hurry, darling.
We're late. Hurry.
- Hey, you!
Wait a second.
Look, I'm not gonna eat ya.
- I just- I just-
It's quiet.
Too quiet.
- WHere is everybody?
- Hey, look at this!
Welcome to DuLoc such a perfect town
Here we have some rules
Let us lay them down
Don't make waves, stay inline
and we'll get along fine
DuLoc is a perfect place
Please keep off of the grass
Shine your shoes, wipe your... face
DuLoc is, DuLoc is
DuLoc is a perfect
- Place
Wow! Let's do that again!
No. No.
No, no, no! No.
Brave knights.
- You are the best and brightest
in the land.
Today one of you
shall prove himself-
All right. You're going the right way
for a smacked bottom.
- Sorry about that.
That champion shall have the honour-
no,no- the privilege...
to go forth and rescue
the lovely Princess Fiona...
from the fiery keep
of the dragon
If for any reason
the winner is unsuccessful,
the fist runner-up
will take his place
and so on and so forth.
Some of you may die, but it's
a sacrifice I am willing to make.
Let the tournament begin!
- Oh!
- What is that?
- It's hideous!
-Ah, that's not very nice.
- It's just a donkey.
Huh?
Indeed. Knights, new plan!
The one who kills the ogre will be
named champion! Have at him!
- Get him!
- Oh, hey! Now come on! Hang on now.
Go ahead! Get him!
Can't we just settle this
over a pint?
Kill the beast!
No? All right then.
Come on!
I don't give a damn
about my reputation
-You've living in the past
It's a new generation
she wants to do
And that's what
I'm gonna do
And I don't give a damn
about my bad reputation
Oh, no, no, no, no, no
Not me
Me, me, me
- Hey, Shrek, tag me! Tag me!
And I don't give a damn
about my reputation
Never said I wanted
to improve my station
Ah!
And I'm always feelin' good
when I'm having fun
And I don't have
to please no one
The chair!
Give him the chair!
And I don't give damn
about my bad reputation
Oh, no, no, no, no, no
Not me
Me, me, me
Oh, no, no, no, no
Not me, not me
-Not me
Oh, yeah! Ah! Ah!
Thank you! Thank you very much!
I'm here till Thursday.
Try the veal! Ha, ha!
Shall I give
the order, sir?
No, I have a better idea.
People of DuLoc,
I give you our champion!
- What?
- Congratulations, ogre.
You've won the honour of
embarking on a great and noble quest.
Quest? I'm already on a quest,
a quest to get my swamp back.
- Your swamp?
- Yeah, my swamp!
Where you dumped
those fairy tale creatures!
- Indeed.
All right, ogre,
I'll make you a deal.
Go on this quest for me, and
I'll give you your swamp back.
Exactly the way it was?
Down to the last
slime-covered toadtool.
- And the squatters?
- As good as gone.
What kind of quest?
Let me get this straight.
You're gonna go fight a dragon...
and rescue a princess just so Farquaad
will give you back a swamp...
which you only don't have because he
filled it full of freaks in the first place.
- Is that about right?
- Maybe there's a good reason donkeys shouldn't talk.
I don't get it. Why don't you just
pull some of that ogre stuff on him?
Throttle him,
lay siege to his fortress,
grind his bones to make your bread,
the whole ogre trip.
Oh, I know what.
Maybe I could have
decapitated an entire village...
and put thier heads
on a pike,
gotten a knife, cut open thier
spleen and drink their fluids.
Does that sound
good to you?
Uh, no, not really, no.
For your information, there's a lot
more to ogres than people think.
- Example?
- Okay, um, ogres are like onions.
- They stink?
- Yes- No! - They
make you cry? - No!
You leave them out in the sun, they get all
brown, start sproutin' little white hairs.
No! Layers!
Onions have layers.
Ogres have layers!
You gt it? We both have layers.
Oh, you both have layers. Oh.
You know, not everybody likes onions.
Cake! Everybody loves cakes!
Cakes have layers.
I don't care...
what everyone likes.
Ogres are not like cakes.
You know what else
everybody likes? Parfaits.
Have you ever met a person, you,
say, "Let's get some parfait,"
they say, "No,
I don't like no parfait"?
- Parfaits are delicious.
- No!
You dense, irritating,
miniature beast of burden!
Ogres are like onions!
End of the story.
Bye-bye. See ya later.
Parfaits may be the most delicious thing
on the whole damn planet.
You know, I think
I preferred your humming.
Do you have a tissue or something?
I'm making a mess.
Just the word parfait
make me start slobbering.
I'm on my way from misery
to happiness today.
Uh-huh, uh-huh
I'm on my way from misery
to happiness today
Uh-huh, uh-huh
And everything
that you receive up yonder
Is what you give to me
the day I wander
I'm on my way
Ooh! Shrek!
Did you do that?
You gotta warn somebody before you
just crack one off. My mouth was open.
Believe me, Donkey, if
it was me, you'd be dead.
It's brimstone.
- We must be getting close.
- Yeah, right, brimstone.
Don't be talking about it's the brimstone. I
know what I smell. It's wasn't no brimstone.
It didn't come off
no stone neither.
Sure, it's big enough,
but look at the location.
Uh, Shrek? Uh, remember when
you said ogres have layers?
Oh, aye.
Well, I have a bit
of a confession to make.
Donkeys don't have layers. We wear
our fear right out there on our sleeves.
- Wait a second. Donkeys don't have sleeves.
- You know what I mean.
You can't tell me
you're afraid of heights.
I'm just a little uncomfortable about being on
a rickely bridge over a boiling lake of lava!
Come on, Donkey.
I'm right here beside ya, okay?
For emotional support,
we'll just tackle this thing
together one little baby stap at a time.
- Really?
- Really, really.
- Okay, that makes me feel so much better.
- Just keep moving.
- And don't look down. Okay,
don't look down. Don't look down.
Don't look down. \Keep on moving. Don't look down.
Shrek! I'm lookin' down!
Oh, God, I can't do this!
Just let me off, please!
- But you're already halfway.
- But I know that half is safe!
Okay, fine. I don't have time for this. You go back.
- Shrek, no! Wait!
- Just, Donkey-
- Let's have a dance then, shall we?
- Don't do that!
Oh, I'm sorry. Do what?
- Oh, this?
- Yes, that!
Yes? Yes, do it. Okay.
No Shrek!
- No! Stop it!
- You said do it! I'm doin' it.
I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die.
Shrek, I'm gonna die.
Oh!
That'll do, Donkey.
That'll do.
Cool.
So where is this
fire-breathing pain-in-the-neck anyway?
Inside, waiting for us
to rescue her.
I was talkin' about the dragon, Shrek.
You afraid?
No, but- Shh.
Oh, good. Me neither.
'Cause there's nothin'
wrong with bein' afraid.
Fear's a sensible response
to an unfamiliar situation.
Unfamiliar dangerous
situation, I might add.
With a dragon that breathes fire
and eats knights and breathes fire,
it sure doesn't mean you're a coward if you're a little scared.
I sure as heck ain't no coward.
I know that.
Donkey, two things, okay?
Shut... up.
Now go over there and see\if you can find any stairs.
Stairs? I thought
we was lookin' for the princess.
The princess will be up the stairs in
the highest room in the tallest tower.
- What makes you think she'll be there?
- I read it in a book once.
Cool. You handle the dragon.
I'll handle the stairs.
I'll find those stairs.
I'll whip their butt too.
Those stairs won't know
which way they're goin'.
I'm gonna take drastic steps.
Kick it to the kerb. Don't mess
with me. I'm the stair master.
I've mastered the stairs. I wish I had
a step right here. I'd step all over it.
Well, at least we know
where the princess is, but where's the-
Dragon!
Donkey, look out!
- Got ya!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Oh! Aah! Aah!
No. Oh, no. No!
- Oh, what large teeth you have.
I mean, white, sparkling teeth. I know you
probably hear this all the time from your food,
but you must bleach, 'cause that
is one dazzling smile you got there.
Do I detect a hint
of minty freshness?
And you know what else?
You're- you're a girl dragon!
Oh, sure! I mean,
of course you're a girl dragon.
You're just reeking
off feminine beauty.
What's the matter with you?
You got something in your eye?
Ooh. Oh. Oh.
Man, I'd really love to stay,
but, you know, I'm, uh-
I'm an asthmatic, and I don't know if it'd
work out if you're gonna blow smoke rings.
Shrek!
No! Shrek! Shrek!
Oh! Oh!
- WAke up!
- What?
Are you Princess Fiona?
I am, awaiting a knight
so bold as to rescue me.
Oh, that's nice.
Now let's go!
But wait, Sir Knight.
This be-ith our first meeting.
Should it not be
a wonderful, romantic moment?
- Yeah, sorry, lady. There's no time.
- Hey, wait. What are you doing?
You should sweep me off my feet...
out yonder window and down a rope
onto your valiant steed.
You've had a lot of time
to plan this, haven't you?
Mm-hmm.
But we have to
savour this moment!
You could recite
an epic poem for me.
A ballad? A sonnet!
- A limerick? Or something!
- I don't think so.
Can I at least know
the name of my champion?
Um, Shrek.
Sir Shrek.
I pray that you take this favour
as a token of my gratitude.
Thanks!
You didn't slay the dragon?
- It's on my to-do list. Now come on!
But this isn't right!
You were meant to charge in,
sword drawn, banner flying.
That's what all
the other knights did.
Yeah, right before
they burst into flame.
That's not the point. Oh!
Wait. Where are you going?
The exit's over there.
Well, I have to save my ass.
What kind of knight are you?
One of a kind.
Slow down. Slow down, baby, please.
I believe it's healthy to get to
know someone over a long period of time.
Just call me old-fashioned.
I don't want to rush into
a physical relationship.
I'm not that emotionally ready
for commitment of, uh, this-
Magnitude really is
the word I'm looking for.
Magnitude- Hey, that is
unwanted physical contact.
Hey, what are you doing?
Okay, okay. Let's just back up a little
and take this one step at a time.
We really should get to know each other
first as friends or pen pals.
I'm on the road a lot, but I just love receiving cards-
I'd really love
to stay, but-
Don't do that. That's my tail!
That's my personal tail.
You're gonna tear it off. I don't give permission
- What are you gonna do with that?
Hey, now. No way.
No! No!
No, no! No.
No, no, no! No! Oh!
- Hi, Princess!
- It talks!
Yeah, it's getting him
to shut up that's the trick.
Oh!
Okay, you two,
head for the exit!
I'll take care of the dragon.
- You did it!
You rescued me!
You're amizing. You're-
You're wonderful. You're...
a little unorthodox I'll admit.
But thy deed is great,
and thine heart is pure.
- I am eternally in your debt.
And where would a brave knight be
without his noble steed?
I hope you heard that. She called me
a noble steed. She think I'm a steed.
The battle is won.
You may remove your helmet,
good Sir Knight.
- Uh, no.
- Why not?
I have helmet hair.
Please. I would'st look
upon the face of my rescuer.
No, no, you wouldn't- 'st.
But how will you kiss me?
What? That wasn't
in the job description.
Maybe it's a perk.
No. It's destiny.
Oh, you must know how it goes.
A princess locked in a tower
and beset by a dragon...
is rescue by a brave knight,
and then they share true love's first kiss.
Hmm? With Shrek?
You think- Wait.
Wait. You think Shrek is your true love?
Well, yes.
You think that Shrek is your true love!
What is so funny?
Let's just say,
I'm not your type, okay?
Of course you are.
You're my rescuer.
Now- Now remove your helmet.
Look. I really don't think
this is a good idea.
- Just take off the helmet.
- I'm not going to.
- Take it off!
- No!
- Now!
- Okay!
Easy. As you command,
Your Highness.
You- You're a- an ogre.
Oh, you were expecting
Prince Charming.
Well, yes, actually.
Oh no. This is all wrong.
You're not supposed
to be an ogre.
Princess, I was sent
to rescue you by Lord Farquaad, okay?
He's the one
who wants to marry you.
Then why didn't
he come to rescue me?
Good question. You should
ask him that when we get there.
But I have to be rescued
by my true love,
not by some ogre and his- his pet.
Well so much for noble steed.
Look princess. You're not making my job any easier.
Well I'm sorry, but your job is not my problem.
You can tell Lord Farquaad
that if he wants to rescue me properly,
I'll be waiting for him
right here.
Hey, I'm no ones messenger boy,
all right? I'm a delivery boy.
You wouldn't dare.
- Ya comin', Donkey?
- Put me down!
Yeah, I'm right behind ya.
Put me down or you will
suffer the consequences!
This is not dignified!
Put me down!
Okay, so here's another question.
Say there's a woman that digs you, right,
but you don't really like her that way.
How do you let her down real easy
so her feelings aren't hurt,
but you don't get burned to a crisp and eaten?
You just tell her
she's not your true love.
Everyone knows it what happens when you find your-
Hey!
The sooner we get to DuLoc the better.
Oh, yeah. You're gonna love it there,
Princess. It's beautiful!
And what of my groom-to-be?
Lord Farquaad? What's he like?
Well, let me put it this way, Princess.
Men of Farquaad's stature
are in short supply.
I don't know. There are those who
think little of him.
Stop it. Stop it,
both of you.
You know, you're just jealous that you can never
measure up to a great ruler like lord Farquaad.
Yeah. Well maybe you're right, Princess.
But I'd let you do the "measuring" when you see him tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
It's take that long?
- Shouldn't we stop to make camp?
- No, that'll take longer.
- We can keep going.
- But there are robbers in the woods.
Whoa! Time out, Shrek!
Camping's starting to sound good.
Hey. Come on. I'm scarier than anything
we're going to see in this forest.
I need to find somewhere to camp now!
- Hey! over here.
- Shrek, we can do better than that.
Now, I don't think this is fit for a princess.
No, no, it's perfect.
It just needs a few homey touches.
- Homey touches? Like what?
A door? Well, gentlemen, I bid thee good night.
Do you want me to come in and read you a bedtime story? 'cause I will.
I said good night!
Shrek, what are you doing?
I just- You know- Oh, come on.
I was just kidding.
And, uh, that one, that's Throwback,
the only ogre to ever spit
over three wheat fields.
Right. Yeah.
Hey, can you tell my future form these stars?
Well, the stars don't tell the future, Donkey.
They tell stories.
Look, there's Bloodnut, the Flatulent.
- You can guess what he is famous for.
- All right. Now I know you're making this up.
No. Look. There he is,
and there's the group of hunters
running away from his stench.
Man, there ain't nothin' but a bunch of little dots.
You know donkey,
sometimes things are more than they appear.
Hmm?
Forget it.
Hey, Shrek, what we gonna do when we get our swamp back, anyway?
Our swamp?
You know. When we're through rescuing the princess and all that stuff.
We? Donkey, there is no "we". There's no "our".
There's just me and my swamp.
And the first thing I'm gonna do is build
a ten-foot wall around my land.
You cut me deep, Shrek.
You cut me real deep just now.
You know what I think?
I think this whole wall thing
is just a way to keep somebody out.
- No, do ya think?
- Are you hidin' something?
Never mind, Donkey.
Oh, this is another one of those onion things, isn't it?
No, this is one of those drop-it and leave-it-alone things.
- Why don't you want to talk about it?
- Why do you want to talk about it?
- Oh, Why you block?
- I'm not blocking.
- Oh yes you are.
- Donkey, I'm warning you.
- Who are you trying to keep out? Just tell me that Shrek. Who?
- Everyone! Okay?
Oh, now we're gettin' somewhere.
Oh, for 'the love of Pete!
Hey, what's your problem Shrek?
What do you got against the whole world anyway?
Look. I'm not the one with the problem, okay?
It's the world that seems to have a problem with me.
People take one look at me and go, "Aah! Help! Run!
A big, stupid, ugly ogre!"
They judge me, before they even know me.
That's why I'm better off alone.
You know what?
When we met, I didn't think you're was just a big, stupid, ugly ogre.
Yeah, I know.
So, uh, are there any donkeys up there?
Well, there's, um, Gabby,
the Small and Annoying.
Okay, okay. I see it, now. The big shiny
one, right there. That's one there?
- That's the moon.
- Oh, okay.
Again. Show me again.
Mirror, mirror, show her to me. Show me the princess.
- Hmph.
Ah. Perfect.
Mmm, yeah, you know I like it like that.
- Oh come on, baby. I said I like it.
- Donkey, wake up.
- Huh? What?
- Wake up.
- What?
- Good morning.
How do you like your eggs?
- Good morning, Princess!
- What's all this about?
You know, we kind of got of to a bad start yesterday.
I wanted to make it up to you.
I mean, after all, you did rescue me.
- Uh, thanks.
Well, eat up. We've got a big day ahead of us.
- Shrek!
What? It's a compliment.
Better out than in, I always say.
- Well, it's no way to behave in front of a princess.
- Thanks
- She's as nasty as you are.
You know, you're not exactly what I expected.
Well, maybe you shouldn't judge people
before you get to know them.
La liberte! Hey!
Princess!
- What are you doing?
Be still, mon cherie, for I am your saviour!
And I am rescuing you from this green-
- beast.
- Hey!
That's my princess! Go find your own!
Please, monster! Can't you see I'm a little busy here?
Look, pal. I don't know who you think you are!
Oh, of course! How rude that was.
Please, let me introduce myself.
Oh, Merry Men!
Ta,dah,dah,dah,whoo
I steal from the rich and give to the needy
- He takes a wee percentage
- But I'm not greedy
I rescue pretty damsels
Man, I'm good
- What a guy, Monsieur Hood
I like an honest fight and a saucy little maid
- What he's basically saying is he likes to get-
- Paid
- So
- When an ogre in the bush grabs a lady by the tush
- That's bad
When a beauty's with a beast it makes me awfully mad
He's mad
He's really, really mad
I'll take my blade and ram it through your heart
Keep your eyes on me, boys 'cause I'm about to start
Man, that was annoying!
Oh, you little...
Um, shall we?
- Hold the phone.
Oh! Whoa!, whoa, whoa. Hold on now.
- Where did that come from?
- What?
That! Back there. That was amazing!
Where did you learn that?
Well- When one lives alone,
uh, one has to learn these things in case there's a-
- There is an arrow in your butt!
- What?
- What? Oh, would you look at that?
- Oh, no. This is all my fault.
- I'm so sorry.
Why? What's wrong?
- Shrek's hurt.
- Shrek's hurt. Shrek's hurt? Oh, no, Shrek's gonna die.
- Donkey, I'm okay.
You can't do this to me Shrek. I'm too young for you to die.
Keep your legs elevated. Turn your head and cough.
- Does anyone know how the Heimlich?
- Donkey! Calm down.
If you want to help Shrek, run into the woods and find me a blue flower with red thorns.
Blue flower, red thorns. Okay, I'm on it. Blue flower, red thorns.
Don't die Shrek. And if you see a long tunnel, stay away from the light!
- Donkey!
- Oh, yeah. Right. Blue Flower, red thorns.
Blue flower, red thorns.
- What are the flowers for?
- For getting rid of the Donkey.
- Ah.
Now you hold still, and I'll yank this thing out.
Ow! Hey! Easy with the yankin'.
- I'm sorry, but it has to come out.
- No, it's tender.
Now, hold on.
What you're doing here is the opposite of help.
- Don't move.
- Look, time out.
- Would you-
Okay. What do you propose we do?
Blue flower, red thorns. Blue flower,
red thorns. Blue flower, red thorns.
This would be so much easier if I wasn't colour-blind!
- Blue flower, red thorns.
- Ow!
Hold on, Shrek! I'm comin'!
Ow! Not good.
- Okay. Okay, I can nearly see the head.
- It's just about-
- Ow! Ohh!
Ahem.
Nothing happened. We were just, uh-
Look, if you wanted to be alone, all you had to do is ask.
Oh, come on! That's the last thing on my mind.
The princess here was just- Ugh!
- Ow!
- Hey, what's that?
That's- Is that blood?
My beloved monster and me
We go everywhere together
Wearin' a raincoat that has four sleeves
- Gets us through all kinds of weather
She will always be the only thing
That comes between me and the awful sting
That comes from living in a world that's so damn mean
Oh, oh-oh-oh-oh
Hey!
- La-la, la-la, la-la-la-la
La-la, la-la, la-la
There it is, Princess.
Your future awaits you.
- That's Duloc?
- Yeah, I know.
You know, Shrek thinks Lord Farquaad's
compensating for something,
which I think means, he has a really- Ow!
Um, I, uh-
- I guess we better move on.
- Sure.
But Shrek?
- I'm- I'm worried about Donkey.
- What?
- I mean, look at him.
- He doesn't look so good.
- What are you talking about? I'm fine.
Well, that's what they always say, and the
next thing you know, you're on your back.
- Dead.
- You know, she's right.
You look awful. Do you want to sit down?
- You know, I'll make you up some tea.
- Well, I didn't want to say nothin',
but I've got this twinge in my neck,
and when I turn my head like this, look.
- Ow! See?
- Who's hungry? I'll find us some dinner.
- I'll get the firewood.
Hey, where are you goin'? Oh man, I can't feel my toes!
I don't have any toes!
I think I need a hug.
Mmm.
Mmm. This is good. This is really good.
- What is this?
- Uh, weedrat.
Rotisserie style.
No kidding.
Well, this is delicious.
Well, they're also great in stews.
Now, I don't mean to brag,
but I make a mean wheedrat stew.
I guess I'll be dining
a little differently tomorrow night.
Maybe you can come visit me in the swamp sometime.
I'll cook all kinds of stuff for you.
Swamp toast soup, fish eye tartare- you name it.
I'd like that.
Um, Princess?
- Yes, Shrek?
- I was wondering
Are, you-
Are you gonna eat that?
Man, isn't this romantic? Just look at that sunset.
- Sunset?
Oh, no! I mean, it's late.
- I-It's very late.
- What?
Wait a minute. I see what's goin' on here.
- You're afraid of the dark, aren't you?
- Yes!
Yes, that's it. I'm terrified. You know I'd better go inside.
But don't feel bad, Princess. I used to be afraid of the dark, too, until-
Hey, no, wait. I'm still afraid of the dark.
- Good night.
Good night.
- Ohh!
Oh, what are you talkin' about?
I don't even wanna hear it. Look, I'm an animal, and I got instincts.
I know that you two are diggin' on each other. I could feel it.
Oh, you're crazy. I'm just bringing her back to Farquaad.
Oh, come on, Shrek. Wake up and smell the pheromones.
- Just go in and tell her how you feel.
- I-
There's nothing to tell. Besides, even if I did tell her that,
well you know-
and I'm not sayin' that I do 'cause I don't-
she's a princess and I'm-
An ogre?
Yeah. An ogre.
- Hey, where are you goin'?
- To get... more firewood.
Princess?
Princess Fiona?
Princess, where are you?
Princess?
It's very spooky in here. I ain't playing no games.
- Aah! - Oh,
no! - No, help!
- Shh! - Shrek! Shrek! Shrek!
- No, it's okay. It's okay.
- What did you do with the princess?
-Donkey, shhh, I'm the princess.
- Aah!
- It's me, in this body.
Oh, my God! You ate the princess!
- Can you hear me? - Donkey!
- Listen, keep breathing! I'll get you out of there!
- No!
- Shrek! Shrek! Shrek!
- Shh.
- Shrek!
- This is me.
Princess?
What happened to you? You're, uh, uh,
uh, different.
- I'm ugly, okay?
- Well, yeah!
Was it something that you ate? 'Cause I told Shrek those rats was a bad idea.
- You are what you eat, I said. Now-
-No.
I- I've been this way as long as I can remember.
What do you mean? Look, I ain't never seen you like this before.
It only happens when the sun goes down.
"By night one way, by day another.
"This shall be the norm...
"until you find true love's first kiss...
and then, take love's true form. "
Ah, that's beautiful. I didn't know you wrote poetry.
It's a spell.
When I was a little girl,
a witch cast a spell on me.
Every night I become this.
This horrible, ugly beast!
I was placed in a tower to await the day my true love would rescue me.
That's why I have to marry lord Farquaad tomorrow...
before the sun sets and he sees me...
like this.
All right, all right. Calm down. Look, it's not that bad.
You're not that ugly. Well, I ain't gonna lie. You are ugly.
But you only look like this at night. Shrek's ugly 24-7.
But Donkey, I'm a princess,
and this is not how a princess is meant to look.
Princess, how 'bout if you don't marry Farquaad?
I have to.
Only my true love's kiss can brake the spell.
But you know, you're kind of an ogre,
and Shrek- well, you've got a lot in common.
Shrek?
Princess, I- Uh, how's it going, first of all?
Good? Um, good for me too.
I'm okay.
I saw this flower and thought of you because it's pretty and-
well, I don't really like it, but I thought you may like it, 'cause you're pretty.
But I like you anyway. I'd- uh, uh-
I'm in trouble. Okay, here we go.
I can't just marry whoever I want.
Take a good look at me, Donkey.
I mean, really,
who could ever love a beast so hideous and hugly?
"Princess" and "ugly" don't go together.
- That's why I can't stay here with Shrek.
My only chance to live happily ever after is to marry my true love.
- Don't you see, Donkey?
That's just how it has to be.
It's the only way to break the spell.
- You at least gotta tell Shrek the truth.
- No!
You can't breathe the word. No one must ever know.
What's the point of being able to talk if you gotta keep secrets?
Promise you won't tell. Promise!
All right, all right. I won't tell him. But you should.
I just know, before this is over, I'm gonna need a whole lot of serious therapy.
- Look at my eye twitchin'.
I tell him, I tell him not.
I tell him.
Shrek!
Shrek, there's something I want-
Shrek.
- Are you all right?
- Perfect!
Never been better.
I- I don't- There's something I have to tell you.
You don't have to tell me anything, Princess.
- I heard enough last night.
- You heard what I said?
Every word.
I thought you'd understand?
Oh, I understand!
Like you said, "Who could love a hideous, ugly beast?"
But I thought that wouldn't matter to you.
Yeah, well, it does.
- Ah, right on time.
Princess, I brought you a little something.
What'd I miss? What'd I miss?
Who said that? Couldn't have been a donkey.
Princess Fiona.
As promised. Now hand it over.
Very well, ogre. The deed to your swamp, cleared out as agreed.
Take it and go before I change my mind.
Forgive me, Princess, for startling you,
but you startled me,
For I've never seen such a radiant beauty before.
I am lord Farquaad.
Lord Farquaad? Oh, no, no.
- Forgive me, my lord, for I was just saying...
a short... farewell.
That is so sweet. You don't have to raise good manners on the ogre.
It's not like it has feelings.
No. You're right. It doesn't.
Princess Fiona, beautiful fair flawless Fiona.
- I ask your hand in marriage.
Will you be the perfect bride for the perfect groom?
Lord Farquaad, I accept. Nothing would make-
Excellent! I'll start the plans for tomorrow we wed!
No! I mean, uh,
Why wait?
Let's get married today before the sun sets.
Oh, anxious, are we? You're right.
The sooner, the better. There's so much to do!
There is the caterer, the cake, the band, the guest list.
Captain, round up some guests.
Fare-thee-well, ogre.
Shrek, what are you doing? You let her get away.
- Yeah? So what?
- Shrek, there's something about her you don't know.
Look, I talked to her last night. She's
Yeah I know you talked to her last night. You're great pals, aren't ya?
Now, if you two are such good friends, why didn't you follow her home?
Shrek, I- I wanna go with you.
I told you, didn't I? You're not coming home with me.
I live alone! My swamp! Me! Nobody else!
Understand? Nobody!
Especially useless, pathetic, annoying, talking donkeys!
- But. I thought
- Yeah. You know what?
You thought wrong!
Shrek.
I heard there was a secret chord
That David played and it pleased the Lord
But you don't really care for music, do ya
It goes like this the fourth, the fifth
The minor fall the major lift
The baffled king composing hallelujah
Hallelujah
Baby, I've been here before
I know this room I've walked this floor
I used to live alone before I knew you
I've seen your flag on the marble arch
But love is not a victory march
It's a cold and it's a broken hallelujah
Hallelujah
And all I ever learned from love
Is how to shoot at someone
- Who outdrew you
And it's not a cry you can hear at night
It's not somebody who's seen the light
- It's a cold and it's a broken hallelujah
Hallelujah
Donkey?
- What are you doing?
I would think, of all the people, you would recognize a wall when you see one.
Well, yeah.
But the wall's supposed to go around my swamp, not through it.
It is around your half. See, that's your half, and this is my half.
Oh, your half? Hmm.
Yes, my half. I helped rescue the princess.
I did half the work, I get half the booty.
Now hand me that big old rock, the one that looks like your head.
- Back off!
- No, you back off.
- This is my swamp!
- Our swamp.
- Let go, Donkey!
- You let go.
- Stubborn jackass!
- Smelly ogre.
Fine!
- Hey, hey, come back here. I'm not through with you yet.
- Well, I'm through with you.
Uh-uh. Well, you know, with you it's always, "Me, me, me!"
Well, guess what! Now it's my turn!
So you just shut up and pay attention!
You are mean to me.
You insult me and you don't appreciate anything that I do!
You're always pushing me around or pushing me away.
Oh, yeah? Well, if I treated you so bad, how come you came back?
Because that's what friend do! They forgive each other!
Oh, yeah. You're right, Donkey.
I forgive you... for stabbin' me in the back!
Ohh! You're so wrapped up in layers, onion boy, you're afraid of your own feelings.
- Go away!
- There you are, doing it again just like you did to Fiona.
And all she ever do was like you, maybe even love you.
Love me? She said I was ugly, a hideous creature.
I heard the two of youtalking.
She wasn't talking about you.
She was talking about, uh, somebody else.
She wasn't talking about me?
Well, then who was she talking about?
Uh-uh, no way. I ain't saying anything. You don't wanna listen to me.
- Right? Right?
- Donkey!
- No!
- Okay, look.
I'm sorry, all right?
Hmph.
I'm sorry.
I guess I am just a big, stupid, ugly ogre.
Can you forgive me?
Hey, that's the friends are for, right?
Right. Friends?
Friends.
So, um,
what did Fiona say about me?
What are you asking me for? Why don't you just go ask her?
The wedding! We'll never make it in time.
Ha-ha-ha! Never fear, for where there's a will, there's a way.
And I have a way.
- Donkey?
I guess this is just my animal magnetism.
Aw, come here, you.
All right, all right. Don't get all slobbery. No one likes a kiss ass.
All right, hop on and hold on tight.
I hadn't have a chance to install seat belts yet.
Whoo!
People of DuLoc,
we gather here today...
to bear witness...
- to the union...
- Um-
- of our new king-
- Excuse me.
- Could we just skip ahead to the "I do's"?
Go on.
Go ahead, have some fun. If we need you, I'll whisle. How about that?
Shrek, wait, wait! Wait a minute!
- You want to do this right, don't you?
- What are you talking about?
There's a line, There's a line you gotta wait for.
The preacher's gonna say, "Speak now or forever hold your peace. "
- That's when you say, "I object!"
- I don't have time for this!
Wait, wait. What are you doing? Listen to me!
- Look, you love this woman, don't you?
- Yes.
- You wanna hold her?
- Please her?
- Yes!
Then you got to, got to try a little tenderness
- The chicks love that romantic crap!
- All right! Cut it out.
- When does this guy say the line?
- We gotta check it out.
- And so, by the power vested in me,
- What do you see?
- The whole town's in there.
- I know pronounce you husband and wife,
- They're at the altar.
- king and queen.
- Mother Fletcher! He already said it.
- Oh, for the love of Pete!
I object!
- Shrek?
Oh, now what does he want?
Hi, everyone. Havin' a good time, are ya?
I love DuLoc, first of all.
- Very clean.
- What are you doing here?
Really, it's rude enough being alive when no one wants you.
- but showing up uninvited to a wedding-
- Fiona!
- I need to talk to you.
- Oh, now you wanna talk?
Well, it's a little late for that, so if you'll excuse me-
- But you can't marry him.
- And why not?
Because- Because he's just marrying you so he can be king.
Outrageous! Fiona, don't listen to him.
- He's not your true love.
- And what do you know about true love?
Well, I- Uh-
I mean-
- Oh, this is precious.
the ogre has fallen in love with the princess!
- Oh, good Lord.
An ogre and a princess!
Shrek, is this true?
Who cares? It's preposterous!
Fiona, my love, we're but a kiss away for our "happily ever after. "
Now kiss me! Mmmm!
"By night one way, by day another. "
I wanted to show you before.
Well, uh,
that explains a lot.
Ugh! It's disgusting!
Guards! Guards!
I order you to get that out of my sight now! Get them!
- Get them both!
- No, no!
This hocus-pocus alters nothing. This marriage is binding, and that makes me king!
- See? See?
- No, let go of me! Shrek!
- No!
Don't just stand there, you morons.
Get out of my way! Fiona!
Arrgh!
I'll make you regret the day we met. I'll see you drawn and quartered!
- You'll beg for death to save you!
- No! Shrek!
- And as for you, my wife.
- Fiona!
I'll have you locked back in that tower for the rest of your days!
- I am king!
I will have order! I will have perfection! I will have-
Aaah!
- Aah!
- All right. Nobody move.
I got a dragon here, and I'm not afraid to use it.
- I'm a donkey on the edge!
Celebrity marriages. They never last, do they?
Go ahead Shrek.
Uh, Fiona?
Yes, Shrek?
I- I love you.
Really?
Really, really.
I love you too.
Aawww!
"Until you find true love's first kiss...
and then take love's true form. "
"Take love's true form. Take love's true form. "
Fiona?
Fiona.
Are you all right?
Well, yes.
But I don't understand.
I'm supposed to be beautiful.
But you are beautiful.
I was hoping this would be a happy ending.
I thought love was only true in fairy tales
Oy!
Meant for someone else but not for me
Love was out to get me
That's the way it seemed
Disappointment haunted all my dreams
And then I saw her face
Now I'm a believer
And not a trace
Of doubt in my mind
- I'm in love
- Ooh-aah
I'm a believer I couldn't leave her
If I tried
God bless us, every one.
Come on, y'all! Ha ha!
Now I'm a believer
Not a trace
Of doubt in my mind
I'm in love Ooh-ahh
I'm a believer I couldn't leave her if I tried
- Ooh!
- Uh!
Then I saw her face
Now I'm a believer
Not a trace
Of doubt in my mind
I'm in love I'm a believer
Come on!
I believe, I believe
I believe, I believe, I believe, hey
Y'all sing it with me!
Believe
I believe
- I believe
- I'm a believer
I believe
Oh, that's funny.
Oh. Oh.
I can't breathe.
I believe in self-assertion
Destiny or a slight divertion
Now it seems I've got my head on straight
I'm freak an apparition
Seems I've made the right decision
To try to turn back now it might be too late
- I want to stay home today
- Don't wanna go out
- If anyone comes to play
- Gonna get thrown out
- I wanna stay home today
- Don't want no company
No way
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I wanna be a millionaire someday
But know what it feels like to give it away
Watch me march to the beat of my own drum
And it's off to the moon and then bak again
Same old day
Same situation
My happiness rears back as if to say
- I wanna stay home today
- Don't wanna go out
- If anyone comes my way
- Gonna get thrown out
- I wanna stay home today
- Don't want no company
No way
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I wanna stay home
stay home, stay home
- I wanna stay home today
- Don't wanna go out
- If anyone comes my way
- Gonna get thrown out
I wanna stay home today
Don't want no company
No way
Yeah, yeah, yeah
I get such a thrill when you look in my eyes
My heart skips a beat
Girl, I feel so alive
Please tell me, baby if all this is true
'Cause deep down inside allI wanted was you
Oh-oh-oh
Makes me wanna dance
It's a new romance
Oh-oh-oh
I look into your eyes
The best years of our lives
When we first met I could hardly believe
The things that would happen and we could achieve
So let's be together for all of our time
Oh, girl, I'm so thankful that you are still mine
You always consider me like an ugly duckling
And treat me like a Nostradamus was why I had to get my shine on
I break a little something to keep my mind on
'Cause you had my mond gone Eh-eh, eh-eh, eh-eh
Turn the lights on, Come on, baby
Let's just rewind the song
'Cause all I want to do is make the rest years the best years
All night long
- Oh-oh-oh, makes me wanna dance
- Makes me wanna dance
- Oh-oh-oh, it's a new romance
- It's a new romance
- Oh-oh-oh, I look into your eyes
- Oh, yeah, yeah
- Look into your eyes
- Oh-oh-oh
- The best years of our lives
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
- Oh-oh-oh, makes me wanna dance
- Whoa-oh-oh, dance, yeah
Oh-oh-oh
It's a new romance
- Oh-oh-oh, i look into your eyes
- Look into your eyes, yeah
Oh-oh-oh
The best years of our lives
Everything looks bright
Standing in your light
Everything feels right
What's left is out of sight
What's a girl to do I'm
telling you You're on my mind
I wanna be with you
'Cause when you're standin' next to me
It's like wow
And all your kisses seem to set me free
And when we touch it's such a rush I can't get enough
It's like- It's like
Ooh-ooh
Hey, what
It's like wow
Ooh-ooh,hey
Hey, yeah
It's like wow
Everything is looking right now, right now
- It's like wow
- And I got this feeling
This feeling it's just like wow
It's just like wow
- You are all I'm thinking of.
Everything feels right
- Like wow
- Everything looks bright
All my senses are right
- Like wow
- Everything feels right
Baby, baby, baby the way I'm feeling you
Is like wow
There is something that I see
In the way you look at me
There's a smile
There's a truth
In your eyes
What an unexpected way
On this unexpected day
Could it be
This is where I belong
It is you I have loved
All along
There's no more mystery
It's finally clear to me
You're the home my heart's searched for
So long
It is you I have loved
All along
Whoa, over and over
I'm filled with emotion
As I look
Into your perfect face